{
  "type": "fill_in_the_blank",
  "title": "Fill in the Blank (1 point per blank, 20 total)",
  "instructions": "Type the correct answer(s) in the blank(s). Do NOT use periods to end your answers. Answers are only things we've discussed in class.",
  "points_per_question": 1,
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "___ was Atari's first hit game.",
      "answers": [["pong"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "In 1981 the US saw the arrival of Shigeru Miyamotoâ€™s arcade game named ___.",
      "answers": [["donkey kong","donkeykong","dk"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "UX stands for ___",
      "answers": [["user experience","userexperience","user exp","userexp"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "The ___ hugely revitalized the video game industry in 1986.",
      "answers": [["nintendo entertainment system","nintendoentertainmentsystem","nes","famicom"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "In MDA, ___ refers to the moment to moment elements of player interaction.",
      "answers": [["mechanics"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List two of the oldest games ever found: ___ and ___.",
      "answers": [["senet", "ur", "mancala", "go"], ["senet", "ur", "mancala", "go"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "The first console wars in the US were between companies ___ and ___.",
      "answers": [["nintendo","sega"], ["nintendo","sega"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Name three ethical issues or dilemmas in video games: ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["violence","addiction","gambling","virtual property","intellectual property","bullying", "false advertising", "diversity", "representation"],
                  ["violence","addiction","gambling","virtual property","intellectual property","bullying", "false advertising", "diversity", "representation"],
                  ["violence","addiction","gambling","virtual property","intellectual property","bullying", "false advertising", "diversity", "representation"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt" : "USPs, as requested by Marketing/PR, stand for ___",
      "answers": [["unique selling points","unique selling point"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "GDD stands for ___",
      "answers": [["game design document","gamedesigndocument"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "TDD stands for ___", 
      "answers": [["technical design document","technicaldesigndocument"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "The Core Game Loop is ___, ___, and ___.",
      "answers": [["input","update","render", "process input", "update game", "render output"],
                  ["input","update","render", "process input", "update game", "render output"],
                  ["input","update","render", "process input", "update game", "render output"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "To ___ is to get changes from the central repository to your local repository.",
      "answers": [["pull","fetch","get"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Scope, cost, and time make up the ___ triangle of quality.",
      "answers": [["iron", "Fe"]]
    }
  ]
}